this past year maybe since my daughter
was born so I felt lost for years
I've struggled with depression and
anxiety and not as much as most a lot of
people have but definitely have suffered
from it and there were a few nights
where it got overwhelming and I just
needed someone to talk to and of course
those things happen it like midnight or
2:00 in the morning and I ended up
calling the suicide prevention hotline
in order to speak with someone I'm like
I just need to speak with something
vanilla not suicidal I shouldn't speak
with someone and there was no one there
and there was like no one answered it
was your hon hold then you're hung up on
I was like like what if I was suicidal
this is a horrible system and I mean I
realize it's because they use people not
counselors but volunteer people who are
trained volunteers in suicide prevention
and they don't have enough of them but I
do think there needs to be a way when
someone is feeling overwhelmed to go on
and say like I need to talk to someone
right now and yes you could put that out
on Facebook but how many of us are going
to do that you know just be I just
opened up too much in our own lives so
to be able to have a conversation with a
stranger is oftentimes a lot more
cathartic and helpful and we don't feel
like we're burdening our family with the
same story over and over again so guess
a stranger chat app but like more for I
really need someone right now so in real
time right now matched with a stranger
and you can say what you want to talk
about not necessarily that you're just
there's a few apps where you can your
match should be there to type or to have
video chat sadly always become sexual
sexualized but that's not the case I
mean having an app it's very much like
hey right now I'm going through a
divorce and I'm silly filly down and a
cat just died and my car broke down and
I just want to Benz and have someone
listen is there someone available and I
think there would always be someone
available especially if you're willing
to do both right you're like I would be
willing to listen to somebody else vent
someone else going through that and it
would speak to them and that would be
who they would be
on to communicate with and I can be very
beneficial so a random matchup let's
vent chat is Apple number 57